public function  Copy() *Regexp
public function  Expand(dst []byte, template []byte, src []byte, match []int) []byte
public function  ExpandString(dst []byte, template string, src string, match []int) []byte
public function  Find(b []byte) []byte
public function  FindAll(b []byte, n int) [][]byte
public function  FindAllIndex(b []byte, n int) [][]int
public function  FindAllString(s string, n int) []string
public function  FindAllStringIndex(s string, n int) [][]int
public function  FindAllStringSubmatch(s string, n int) [][]string
public function  FindAllStringSubmatchIndex(s string, n int) [][]int
public function  FindAllSubmatch(b []byte, n int) [][][]byte
public function  FindAllSubmatchIndex(b []byte, n int) [][]int
public function  FindIndex(b []byte) (loc []int)
public function  FindReaderIndex(r io.RuneReader) (loc []int)
public function  FindReaderSubmatchIndex(r io.RuneReader) []int
public function  FindString(s string) string
public function  FindStringIndex(s string) (loc []int)
public function  FindStringSubmatch(s string) []string
public function  FindStringSubmatchIndex(s string) []int
public function  FindSubmatch(b []byte) [][]byte
public function  FindSubmatchIndex(b []byte) []int
public function  LiteralPrefix() (prefix string, complete bool)
public function  Longest()
public function  MarshalText() ([]byte, error)
public function  Match(b []byte) bool
public function  MatchReader(r io.RuneReader) bool
public function  MatchString(s string) bool
public function  NumSubexp() int
public function  ReplaceAll(src, repl []byte) []byte
public function  ReplaceAllFunc(src []byte, repl func([]byte) []byte) []byte
public function  ReplaceAllLiteral(src, repl []byte) []byte
public function  ReplaceAllLiteralString(src, repl string) string
public function  ReplaceAllString(src, repl string) string
public function  ReplaceAllStringFunc(src string, repl func(string) string) string
public function  Split(s string, n int) []string
public function  String() string
public function  SubexpIndex(name string) int
public function  SubexpNames() []string
public function  UnmarshalText(text []byte) error
